wherezit.com 2018-01-25

# Wherezit.com - Privacy Policy

### WherezIt.com Privacy Policy

Last Updated April, 2006 

Here at WherezIt.com we understand that privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect when you use WherezIt.com's services, as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. We hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to Contact Us. 

In order to access the information available at WherezIt.com, you do not need to register or provide any personal information. A user may register in order to personalize the display of information and simplify the access to some information. A user is required to register only when they will be posting information on the site that will be seen by others.

**Information we collect and how we use it:**

Information you provide - When you register for a WherezIt.com Account, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). For certain services, such as creating a listing, we also request credit card or other payment account information, which we maintain in encrypted form on secure servers. We also allow the user to enter address and phone number information that they may, at their option share.

WherezIt.com cookies - When you visit WherezIt.com, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some WherezIt.com features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

Log information - When you use WherezIt.com services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

User communications - When you send email or other communication to WherezIt.com, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

Links - WherezIt.com may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our services. We do not provide your personal information to these sites when you follow these links.

Other sites - This Privacy Policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and operated by WherezIt.com. We do not exercise control over other sites. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. They will not receive your personal information from WherezIt.com.

Other Purposes - Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services; Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and Developing new services.

WherezIt.com processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America.

**Choices for personal information**

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. This information will not be shared with out your explicit consent.

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case WherezIt.com may not be able to provide those services to you.

**Information sharing**

WherezIt.com only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of WherezIt.com in the following limited circumstances:

We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any personal information.

Information will be shared with financial institutions as needed for the purpose of payment processing.

We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of WherezIt.com, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If WherezIt.com becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who accessed a particular listing, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular listing. Such information does not identify you individually.

**Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to WherezIt.com employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

**Data integrity**

WherezIt.com processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

**Accessing and updating personal information**

When you use WherezIt.com services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort.

**Enforcement**

WherezIt.com regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or WherezIt.com's treatment of personal information by contacting us.

**Changes to this policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.
